

Maria Montagu UI/UX Designer

About me

With a passion for creating great user interfaces, I bring together my marketing and technical background to design effective and exceptional user experiences.

As a versatile professional in frontend development and UI/UX design, I love learning and collaborating to bring a multidimensional approach to every project I undertake.



Contact

- +33 6 31 30 76 30
- mariafmontagu@gmail.com
- in linkedin.com/in/mariafmontagu
- https://mafemont16.github.io/portfolio/
- ♥ Marseille, France

Technical skills

Technologies

HTML, CSS, Material UI, React.js, JavaScript, TypeScript.

Content management systems

WordPress

Project management tools

Git, GitHub, Jira, Bitbucket

Tools

Figma Notion Microsoft Office Visual Studio Code ZeroHeight

Languages

Spanish : native French : intermediate English : fluent

Hobbies

Running Reading

Professional experience

UI / UX designer

SYSTRA - MARSEILLE | OCTOBER 2022 - MAY 2023

- Used different UX methodologies to assess different mobility platforms, updated their Design System using Figma and ZeroHeight for documentation
- Created wireframes, prototypes, and high-fidelity designs using Figma.
- Collaborated with stakeholders to define user requirements and design intuitive interfaces for complex construction applications.

Front-end Developer

SUBCLIC - MARSEILLE | JULY 2021 - SEPT. 2022

 Contributed to the development of the Back-office's frontend using a robust tech stack including React.js, TypeScript, Material UI, GraphQL, and Webpack.

Customer Success Associate

TRAXENS | SEPT. 2019 - MAR. 2020

 Led project setup and demos for new customers, including CMA CGM and MSC, using Traxens IOT solution as a Customer Success Associate. Provided technical support for smart container projects.

Marketing Project Manager

NCC PARTNERS | AUG. 2018 - JULY 2019

 Planned and executed the highly successful International Mobile Gaming Awards event in San Francisco, strategically targeting gaming companies and game developers to foster industry connections and recognition.

Marketing Manager

DÉCOUVERTES | JAN. 2017 - JULY 2018

 Implemented effective marketing strategies and streamlined processes by leveraging the HubSpot CRM platform.

Education

2020 - 2021 Full-stack web development training

ÉCOLE CENTRALE DE MARSEILLE

PASSERELLE NUMÉRIQUE

9 months training in full-stack web development (front-end and back-end web development, databases, algorithms, agile

methods, CMS).

<u>www.passerelle-numerique.fr</u>

2015 - 2016 M.Sc. Marketing - Brand Management

KEDGE BUSINESS SCHOOL - MARSEILLE

2006 - 2010 **B.sc. Economics**

UNIV. PONTIFICIA BOLIVARIANA - COLOMBIA